It's raining!
Sta piovendo!
Oh no
Oh, no!
Paimon forgot to bring an umbrella...
Paimon ha dimenticato l'ombrello...
Come on
Forza!
Let's hurry before it rains harder!
Sbrighiamoci prima che peggiori!
Ugh, it's raining again?
Argh, piove di nuovo?
I've had enough of this weather
Questo tempo mi ha stufato.
There go my travel plans...
Tanti saluti ai miei piani di viaggio...
Did you read the news this morning?
Hai letto la notizia di stamane?
Quick
Presto!
Put away everything on the clotheslines!
Prendi i panni stesi!
When is this rain going to stop...
Quando finirà questa pioggia?
Hydro Dragon, Hydro Dragon, don't cry!
Drago di Hydro, Drago di Hydro, non piangere!
They're planning to reanimate the monster...
Stanno cercando di rianimare il mostro...
We have to report this to the Chief Justice
Dobbiamo riferirlo al Giudice supremo!
The Fortress of Meropide...
Forte Méropide...
It's a good place for me
È un buon posto per me.
He owes me so many answers...
Mi deve molte spiegazioni...
Neuvillette?
Neuvillette?
You could say he's the real symbol of Fontaine's justice
Possiamo dire che è il simbolo della giustizia a Fontaine.
Watch him closely
Tenetelo d'occhio.
He could be trouble
Potrebbe creare problemi.
How can two completely different species possibly coexist?
Come possono coesistere due specie così diverse?
Who's been threatening Melusines?
Chi è che minaccia le Melusine?
Show yourself!
Fatti vedere!
You will see much
Ammirerai molto
In the human world
del mondo umano...
From the delightful to the depressing...
Cose belle e cose spiacevoli.
And one day, when you have dwelt among humanity long enough
E un giorno, dopo aver vissuto abbastanza tra l'umanità,
You will be placed to bring judgment over all
emetterai il tuo giudizio su ogni cosa,
As the spokesperson for Fontaine's past
come portavoce del passato di Fontaine.
Good morning, Monsieur Neuvillette!
Buongiorno, Messire Neuvillette.
The rainy season's almost over...
La stagione delle piogge è quasi finita...
I hope you find time to enjoy the sunny days ahead
Spero tanto che si godrà i giorni di sole che verranno.